pufcigs.com 2016-04-08

# Privacy Policy Puf

Puf Cigs Inc. has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering practices for all of Puf Cigs websites.

Puf Cigs has established a privacy policy with the mission of building member trust and confidence by promoting the use of fair information practices. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact billing@pufcigs.com

This site is owned and operated by Puf Cigs Inc.

Puf Cigs Inc.  
P.O. Box 80477  
Staten Island, NY 10308

Customer Service Department: 1.855.PUF.CIGS

### Cookies

Puf Cigs uses session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. For more information on cookies click here.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as username and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user special offers and updates from Puf Cigs. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the person when necessary.

### Choice/Opt-out

As an individual, you have the opportunity to limit the personal information you provide. We provide you with the opportunity to 'opt out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt out of receiving them by contacting us at billing@pufcigs.com.

## Information Collection & Use

### Registration

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information including your name and email address. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

Puf Cigs is the sole owner of the information collected on www.Puf Cigscigs.com. Puf Cigs collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page, emailing our Customer Support at billing @ pufcigs.com or contacting us by telephone or postal mail using the information located at the top of this page.

### Surveys or Contests

From time to time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code). We may request other information, in our sole discretion, which we consider important to the administration and promotion of the survey or contest

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, monitor site traffic, personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), and send participants an email newsletter. We may also use this information for publicity or marketing purposes. We may publish this information in our sole discretion. The rules applicable to any individual survey or contest will be published prior to the collection of any personally identifiable information and you agree to such use by submitting any information.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company is prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

## Uses of Information

### Email

Puf Cigs members and affiliates receive periodic email notices that include exclusive special offers and information about sales, promotions, new releases, and other relevant information. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt out by contacting us at billing@pufcigs.com

### Non-personal information

Like many web sites, we collect and analyze standard log file information and Session ID information to analyze site traffic, improve site performance, and prevent fraud. Session IDs are bits of code on your computer that assist your browser in navigating our site. We do not associate personal information with log file information or cookies, except when needed to prevent fraud.

### Affiliate and Webmaster sign-up

Puf Cigs collects prospective affiliate and webmaster contact information to process applications and conduct business. This information includes: name, checks payable, address, city, state/province, country, minimum payout, password, source of referral, tax ID (EIN or social security number for U.S. residents), and date of birth.

## Legal Disclaimer

Puf Cigs reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our web site.

The Puf Cigs web site(s) contains links to other sites. Puf Cigs is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. Our site uses a secure online ordering system that enables clients to purchase products online. Puf Cigs collects users' financial information, such as account and credit card numbers, for verification purposes only. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services, and never for any other reason.

###   
Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link: GoDaddy

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of online transmission or electronic storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our web site, you can email us at info @ pufcigs.com

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at shop@pufcigs.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Puf Cigs Inc. P.O. Box 80477. Staten Island, NY 10308 .

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name| COOKIE Description  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CURRENCY | Your preferred currency  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | Stores the Customer Segment ID  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
FRONTEND | You sesssion ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.
